[
  {
    "Number": 1,
    "Question": "If a solution is 85 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 110 ml",
    "Answer": 9350,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 2,
    "Question": "If a solution is 70 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 2 l",
    "Answer": 140,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 3,
    "Question": "If a solution is 2 mg/100 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 200 ml",
    "Answer": 4,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 4,
    "Question": "If a solution is 3.5 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 60 ml",
    "Answer": 2.1,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 5,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 2.5 g/100 g, how many g are required to make a total of 250 g",
    "Answer": 6.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 6,
    "Question": "If a solution is 1 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 30 ml",
    "Answer": 0.3,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 7,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 9 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 100 g",
    "Answer": 9,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 8,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 45 g",
    "Answer": 450,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 9,
    "Question": "If a solution is 75 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 110 ml",
    "Answer": 8250,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 10,
    "Question": "If a solution is 75 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 1 l",
    "Answer": 75,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 11,
    "Question": "If a solution is 3 mg/70 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 210 ml",
    "Answer": 9,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 12,
    "Question": "If a solution is 8 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 45 ml",
    "Answer": 3.6,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 13,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 6 g/60 g, how many g are required to make a total of 360 g",
    "Answer": 36,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 14,
    "Question": "If a solution is 5 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 25 ml",
    "Answer": 1.25,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 15,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 8 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 75 g",
    "Answer": 6,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 16,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1.5 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 40 g",
    "Answer": 600,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 17,
    "Question": "If a solution is 10 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 45 ml",
    "Answer": 450,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 18,
    "Question": "If a solution is 40 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 0.5 l",
    "Answer": 20,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 19,
    "Question": "If a solution is 6 mg/40 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 240 ml",
    "Answer": 36,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 20,
    "Question": "If a solution is 2.5 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 75 ml",
    "Answer": 1.875,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 21,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1.5 g/100 g, how many g are required to make a total of 150 g",
    "Answer": 2.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 22,
    "Question": "If a solution is 4 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 85 ml",
    "Answer": 3.4,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 23,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 3.5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 15 g",
    "Answer": 0.525,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 24,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 0.5 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 60 g",
    "Answer": 300,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 25,
    "Question": "If a solution is 30 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 5 ml",
    "Answer": 150,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 26,
    "Question": "If a solution is 90 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 2 l",
    "Answer": 180,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 27,
    "Question": "If a solution is 4 mg/20 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 80 ml",
    "Answer": 16,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 28,
    "Question": "If a solution is 5 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 45 ml",
    "Answer": 2.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 29,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 3 g/10 g, how many g are required to make a total of 30 g",
    "Answer": 9,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 30,
    "Question": "If a solution is 3 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 5 ml",
    "Answer": 0.15,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 31,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 8.5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 35 g",
    "Answer": 2.975,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 32,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1.5 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 20 g",
    "Answer": 300,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 33,
    "Question": "If a solution is 115 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 35 ml",
    "Answer": 4025,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 34,
    "Question": "If a solution is 75 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 1.5 l",
    "Answer": 112.5,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 35,
    "Question": "If a solution is 4 mg/30 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 120 ml",
    "Answer": 16,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 36,
    "Question": "If a solution is 1 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 55 ml",
    "Answer": 0.55,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 37,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 2 g/80 g, how many g are required to make a total of 160 g",
    "Answer": 4,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 38,
    "Question": "If a solution is 9 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 110 ml",
    "Answer": 9.9,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 39,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 4.5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 110 g",
    "Answer": 4.95,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 40,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 2 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 50 g",
    "Answer": 1000,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 41,
    "Question": "If a solution is 35 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 85 ml",
    "Answer": 2975,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 42,
    "Question": "If a solution is 35 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 0.5 l",
    "Answer": 17.5,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 43,
    "Question": "If a solution is 1.5 mg/100 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 150 ml",
    "Answer": 2.25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 44,
    "Question": "If a solution is 6.5 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 20 ml",
    "Answer": 1.3,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 45,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1.5 g/100 g, how many g are required to make a total of 150 g",
    "Answer": 2.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 46,
    "Question": "If a solution is 7.5 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 90 ml",
    "Answer": 6.75,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 47,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 6 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 50 g",
    "Answer": 3,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 48,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 20 g",
    "Answer": 200,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 49,
    "Question": "If a solution is 110 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 60 ml",
    "Answer": 6600,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 50,
    "Question": "If a solution is 70 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 0.5 l",
    "Answer": 35,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 51,
    "Question": "If a solution is 4.5 mg/70 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 315 ml",
    "Answer": 20.25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 52,
    "Question": "If a solution is 8 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 85 ml",
    "Answer": 6.8,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 53,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 4.5 g/80 g, how many g are required to make a total of 360 g",
    "Answer": 20.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 54,
    "Question": "If a solution is 2 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 60 ml",
    "Answer": 1.2,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 55,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 100 g",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 56,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 2 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 15 g",
    "Answer": 300,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 57,
    "Question": "If a solution is 125 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 25 ml",
    "Answer": 3125,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 58,
    "Question": "If a solution is 105 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 0.5 l",
    "Answer": 52.5,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 59,
    "Question": "If a solution is 4 mg/100 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 400 ml",
    "Answer": 16,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 60,
    "Question": "If a solution is 9 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 55 ml",
    "Answer": 4.95,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 61,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 3.5 g/40 g, how many g are required to make a total of 140 g",
    "Answer": 12.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 62,
    "Question": "If a solution is 4.5 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 65 ml",
    "Answer": 2.925,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 63,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 6 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 15 g",
    "Answer": 0.9,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 64,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1.5 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 25 g",
    "Answer": 375,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 65,
    "Question": "If a solution is 70 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 90 ml",
    "Answer": 6300,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 66,
    "Question": "If a solution is 95 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 0.5 l",
    "Answer": 47.5,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 67,
    "Question": "If a solution is 5 mg/50 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 250 ml",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 68,
    "Question": "If a solution is 5 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 100 ml",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 69,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 6 g/40 g, how many g are required to make a total of 240 g",
    "Answer": 36,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 70,
    "Question": "If a solution is 2.5 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 125 ml",
    "Answer": 3.125,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 71,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 9 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 55 g",
    "Answer": 4.95,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 72,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 0.5 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 60 g",
    "Answer": 300,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 73,
    "Question": "If a solution is 115 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 120 ml",
    "Answer": 13800,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 74,
    "Question": "If a solution is 55 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 1.5 l",
    "Answer": 82.5,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 75,
    "Question": "If a solution is 2.5 mg/100 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 250 ml",
    "Answer": 6.25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 76,
    "Question": "If a solution is 4 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 60 ml",
    "Answer": 2.4,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 77,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1.5 g/10 g, how many g are required to make a total of 15 g",
    "Answer": 2.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 78,
    "Question": "If a solution is 3.5 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 5 ml",
    "Answer": 0.175,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 79,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 25 g",
    "Answer": 1.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 80,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 2 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 25 g",
    "Answer": 500,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 81,
    "Question": "If a solution is 40 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 20 ml",
    "Answer": 800,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 82,
    "Question": "If a solution is 55 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 1 l",
    "Answer": 55,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 83,
    "Question": "If a solution is 5 mg/80 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 400 ml",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 84,
    "Question": "If a solution is 7 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 40 ml",
    "Answer": 2.8,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 85,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 6 g/60 g, how many g are required to make a total of 360 g",
    "Answer": 36,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 86,
    "Question": "If a solution is 7.5 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 35 ml",
    "Answer": 2.625,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 87,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 6.5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 50 g",
    "Answer": 3.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 88,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 0.5 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 55 g",
    "Answer": 275,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 89,
    "Question": "If a solution is 25 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 80 ml",
    "Answer": 2000,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 90,
    "Question": "If a solution is 35 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 2 l",
    "Answer": 70,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 91,
    "Question": "If a solution is 2 mg/50 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 100 ml",
    "Answer": 4,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 92,
    "Question": "If a solution is 9 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 95 ml",
    "Answer": 8.55,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 93,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 4 g/100 g, how many g are required to make a total of 400 g",
    "Answer": 16,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 94,
    "Question": "If a solution is 2 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 90 ml",
    "Answer": 1.8,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 95,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1.5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 120 g",
    "Answer": 1.8,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 96,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 70 g",
    "Answer": 700,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 97,
    "Question": "If a solution is 95 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 115 ml",
    "Answer": 10925,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 98,
    "Question": "If a solution is 80 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 1.5 l",
    "Answer": 120,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 99,
    "Question": "If a solution is 3 mg/90 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 270 ml",
    "Answer": 9,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 100,
    "Question": "If a solution is 5 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 125 ml",
    "Answer": 6.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 101,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 3 g/90 g, how many g are required to make a total of 270 g",
    "Answer": 9,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 102,
    "Question": "If a solution is 3.5 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 35 ml",
    "Answer": 1.225,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 103,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 8 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 5 g",
    "Answer": 0.4,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 104,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1.5 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 15 g",
    "Answer": 225,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 105,
    "Question": "If a solution is 60 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 75 ml",
    "Answer": 4500,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 106,
    "Question": "If a solution is 40 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 1 l",
    "Answer": 40,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 107,
    "Question": "If a solution is 2.5 mg/50 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 125 ml",
    "Answer": 6.25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 108,
    "Question": "If a solution is 7.5 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 35 ml",
    "Answer": 2.625,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 109,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 2 g/80 g, how many g are required to make a total of 160 g",
    "Answer": 4,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 110,
    "Question": "If a solution is 9 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 90 ml",
    "Answer": 8.1,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 111,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 3.5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 75 g",
    "Answer": 2.625,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 112,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1.5 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 70 g",
    "Answer": 1050,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 113,
    "Question": "If a solution is 40 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 55 ml",
    "Answer": 2200,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 114,
    "Question": "If a solution is 40 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 0.5 l",
    "Answer": 20,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 115,
    "Question": "If a solution is 2 mg/90 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 180 ml",
    "Answer": 4,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 116,
    "Question": "If a solution is 6 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 105 ml",
    "Answer": 6.3,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 117,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1.5 g/40 g, how many g are required to make a total of 60 g",
    "Answer": 2.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 118,
    "Question": "If a solution is 3 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 115 ml",
    "Answer": 3.45,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 119,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 5.5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 50 g",
    "Answer": 2.75,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 120,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 35 g",
    "Answer": 350,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 121,
    "Question": "If a solution is 80 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 10 ml",
    "Answer": 800,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 122,
    "Question": "If a solution is 70 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 1 l",
    "Answer": 70,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 123,
    "Question": "If a solution is 4.5 mg/60 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 270 ml",
    "Answer": 20.25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 124,
    "Question": "If a solution is 7 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 50 ml",
    "Answer": 3.5,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 125,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 4 g/80 g, how many g are required to make a total of 320 g",
    "Answer": 16,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 126,
    "Question": "If a solution is 1 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 30 ml",
    "Answer": 0.3,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 127,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 20 g",
    "Answer": 1,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 128,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 2 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 50 g",
    "Answer": 1000,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 129,
    "Question": "If a solution is 120 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 15 ml",
    "Answer": 1800,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 130,
    "Question": "If a solution is 70 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 2 l",
    "Answer": 140,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 131,
    "Question": "If a solution is 3 mg/80 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 240 ml",
    "Answer": 9,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 132,
    "Question": "If a solution is 3 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 55 ml",
    "Answer": 1.65,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 133,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 3 g/30 g, how many g are required to make a total of 90 g",
    "Answer": 9,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 134,
    "Question": "If a solution is 2 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 15 ml",
    "Answer": 0.3,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 135,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 65 g",
    "Answer": 3.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 136,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1.5 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 5 g",
    "Answer": 75,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 137,
    "Question": "If a solution is 95 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 55 ml",
    "Answer": 5225,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 138,
    "Question": "If a solution is 85 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 1 l",
    "Answer": 85,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 139,
    "Question": "If a solution is 5 mg/40 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 200 ml",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 140,
    "Question": "If a solution is 8 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 85 ml",
    "Answer": 6.8,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 141,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1.5 g/20 g, how many g are required to make a total of 30 g",
    "Answer": 2.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 142,
    "Question": "If a solution is 10 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 125 ml",
    "Answer": 12.5,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 143,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 2.5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 40 g",
    "Answer": 1,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 144,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1.5 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 65 g",
    "Answer": 975,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 145,
    "Question": "If a solution is 10 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 95 ml",
    "Answer": 950,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 146,
    "Question": "If a solution is 45 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 2 l",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 147,
    "Question": "If a solution is 6 mg/10 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 60 ml",
    "Answer": 36,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 148,
    "Question": "If a solution is 4 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 110 ml",
    "Answer": 4.4,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 149,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1.5 g/80 g, how many g are required to make a total of 120 g",
    "Answer": 2.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 150,
    "Question": "If a solution is 5 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 95 ml",
    "Answer": 4.75,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 151,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 4 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 25 g",
    "Answer": 1,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 152,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1.5 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 25 g",
    "Answer": 375,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 153,
    "Question": "If a solution is 75 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 125 ml",
    "Answer": 9375,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 154,
    "Question": "If a solution is 60 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 0.5 l",
    "Answer": 30,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 155,
    "Question": "If a solution is 5 mg/50 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 250 ml",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 156,
    "Question": "If a solution is 1 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 15 ml",
    "Answer": 0.15,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 157,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 3.5 g/20 g, how many g are required to make a total of 70 g",
    "Answer": 12.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 158,
    "Question": "If a solution is 9 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 35 ml",
    "Answer": 3.15,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 159,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 6.5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 105 g",
    "Answer": 6.825,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 160,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 0.5 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 25 g",
    "Answer": 125,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 161,
    "Question": "If a solution is 30 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 30 ml",
    "Answer": 900,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 162,
    "Question": "If a solution is 110 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 1.5 l",
    "Answer": 165,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 163,
    "Question": "If a solution is 2.5 mg/40 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 100 ml",
    "Answer": 6.25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 164,
    "Question": "If a solution is 7.5 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 70 ml",
    "Answer": 5.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 165,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 6 g/70 g, how many g are required to make a total of 420 g",
    "Answer": 36,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 166,
    "Question": "If a solution is 10 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 50 ml",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 167,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 7.5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 85 g",
    "Answer": 6.375,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 168,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 2 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 55 g",
    "Answer": 1100,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 169,
    "Question": "If a solution is 125 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 105 ml",
    "Answer": 13125,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 170,
    "Question": "If a solution is 40 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 1.5 l",
    "Answer": 60,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 171,
    "Question": "If a solution is 2.5 mg/80 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 200 ml",
    "Answer": 6.25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 172,
    "Question": "If a solution is 10 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 30 ml",
    "Answer": 3,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 173,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 3.5 g/80 g, how many g are required to make a total of 280 g",
    "Answer": 12.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 174,
    "Question": "If a solution is 1.5 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 5 ml",
    "Answer": 0.075,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 175,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 2.5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 120 g",
    "Answer": 3,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 176,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1.5 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 75 g",
    "Answer": 1125,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 177,
    "Question": "If a solution is 25 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 45 ml",
    "Answer": 1125,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 178,
    "Question": "If a solution is 100 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 0.5 l",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 179,
    "Question": "If a solution is 3 mg/40 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 120 ml",
    "Answer": 9,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 180,
    "Question": "If a solution is 8.5 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 10 ml",
    "Answer": 0.85,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 181,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 4.5 g/20 g, how many g are required to make a total of 90 g",
    "Answer": 20.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 182,
    "Question": "If a solution is 8 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 80 ml",
    "Answer": 6.4,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 183,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 10 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 45 g",
    "Answer": 4.5,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 184,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1.5 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 35 g",
    "Answer": 525,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 185,
    "Question": "If a solution is 105 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 75 ml",
    "Answer": 7875,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 186,
    "Question": "If a solution is 120 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 1.5 l",
    "Answer": 180,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 187,
    "Question": "If a solution is 6 mg/100 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 600 ml",
    "Answer": 36,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 188,
    "Question": "If a solution is 1.5 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 95 ml",
    "Answer": 1.425,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 189,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 6 g/10 g, how many g are required to make a total of 60 g",
    "Answer": 36,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 190,
    "Question": "If a solution is 4 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 90 ml",
    "Answer": 3.6,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 191,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 115 g",
    "Answer": 1.15,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 192,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 0.5 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 20 g",
    "Answer": 100,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 193,
    "Question": "If a solution is 80 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 110 ml",
    "Answer": 8800,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 194,
    "Question": "If a solution is 25 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 1 l",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 195,
    "Question": "If a solution is 4.5 mg/50 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 225 ml",
    "Answer": 20.25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 196,
    "Question": "If a solution is 3.5 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 60 ml",
    "Answer": 2.1,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 197,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 3.5 g/80 g, how many g are required to make a total of 280 g",
    "Answer": 12.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 198,
    "Question": "If a solution is 6.5 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 85 ml",
    "Answer": 5.525,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 199,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 3 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 105 g",
    "Answer": 3.15,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 200,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 0.5 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 40 g",
    "Answer": 200,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 201,
    "Question": "If a solution is 90 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 100 ml",
    "Answer": 9000,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 202,
    "Question": "If a solution is 25 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 2 l",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 203,
    "Question": "If a solution is 3 mg/50 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 150 ml",
    "Answer": 9,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 204,
    "Question": "If a solution is 1.5 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 120 ml",
    "Answer": 1.8,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 205,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 2.5 g/100 g, how many g are required to make a total of 250 g",
    "Answer": 6.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 206,
    "Question": "If a solution is 3 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 115 ml",
    "Answer": 3.45,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 207,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 0.5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 10 g",
    "Answer": 0.05,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 208,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1.5 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 75 g",
    "Answer": 1125,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 209,
    "Question": "If a solution is 50 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 65 ml",
    "Answer": 3250,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 210,
    "Question": "If a solution is 105 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 2 l",
    "Answer": 210,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 211,
    "Question": "If a solution is 2 mg/10 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 20 ml",
    "Answer": 4,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 212,
    "Question": "If a solution is 3.5 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 20 ml",
    "Answer": 0.7,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 213,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1.5 g/30 g, how many g are required to make a total of 45 g",
    "Answer": 2.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 214,
    "Question": "If a solution is 5 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 75 ml",
    "Answer": 3.75,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 215,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 9.5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 15 g",
    "Answer": 1.425,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 216,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1.5 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 50 g",
    "Answer": 750,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 217,
    "Question": "If a solution is 80 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 40 ml",
    "Answer": 3200,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 218,
    "Question": "If a solution is 25 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 1.5 l",
    "Answer": 37.5,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 219,
    "Question": "If a solution is 1.5 mg/70 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 105 ml",
    "Answer": 2.25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 220,
    "Question": "If a solution is 1.5 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 50 ml",
    "Answer": 0.75,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 221,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1.5 g/80 g, how many g are required to make a total of 120 g",
    "Answer": 2.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 222,
    "Question": "If a solution is 2 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 105 ml",
    "Answer": 2.1,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 223,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 6 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 85 g",
    "Answer": 5.1,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 224,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 0.5 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 25 g",
    "Answer": 125,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 225,
    "Question": "If a solution is 15 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 85 ml",
    "Answer": 1275,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 226,
    "Question": "If a solution is 70 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 0.5 l",
    "Answer": 35,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 227,
    "Question": "If a solution is 3 mg/10 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 30 ml",
    "Answer": 9,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 228,
    "Question": "If a solution is 7.5 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 115 ml",
    "Answer": 8.625,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 229,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 4 g/90 g, how many g are required to make a total of 360 g",
    "Answer": 16,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 230,
    "Question": "If a solution is 7 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 15 ml",
    "Answer": 1.05,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 231,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 4 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 35 g",
    "Answer": 1.4,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 232,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 2 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 10 g",
    "Answer": 200,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 233,
    "Question": "If a solution is 125 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 125 ml",
    "Answer": 15625,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 234,
    "Question": "If a solution is 85 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 1 l",
    "Answer": 85,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 235,
    "Question": "If a solution is 3.5 mg/20 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 70 ml",
    "Answer": 12.25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 236,
    "Question": "If a solution is 7 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 40 ml",
    "Answer": 2.8,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 237,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 4.5 g/70 g, how many g are required to make a total of 315 g",
    "Answer": 20.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 238,
    "Question": "If a solution is 7 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 35 ml",
    "Answer": 2.45,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 239,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 0.5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 120 g",
    "Answer": 0.6,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 240,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 0.5 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 45 g",
    "Answer": 225,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 241,
    "Question": "If a solution is 105 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 65 ml",
    "Answer": 6825,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 242,
    "Question": "If a solution is 35 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 2 l",
    "Answer": 70,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 243,
    "Question": "If a solution is 2.5 mg/90 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 225 ml",
    "Answer": 6.25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 244,
    "Question": "If a solution is 0.5 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 10 ml",
    "Answer": 0.05,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 245,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 3.5 g/70 g, how many g are required to make a total of 245 g",
    "Answer": 12.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 246,
    "Question": "If a solution is 1.5 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 100 ml",
    "Answer": 1.5,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 247,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 4.5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 100 g",
    "Answer": 4.5,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 248,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 20 g",
    "Answer": 200,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 249,
    "Question": "If a solution is 65 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 25 ml",
    "Answer": 1625,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 250,
    "Question": "If a solution is 100 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 0.5 l",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 251,
    "Question": "If a solution is 1.5 mg/30 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 45 ml",
    "Answer": 2.25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 252,
    "Question": "If a solution is 8.5 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 40 ml",
    "Answer": 3.4,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 253,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 4.5 g/30 g, how many g are required to make a total of 135 g",
    "Answer": 20.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 254,
    "Question": "If a solution is 6.5 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 50 ml",
    "Answer": 3.25,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 255,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 10 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 80 g",
    "Answer": 8,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 256,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1.5 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 15 g",
    "Answer": 225,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 257,
    "Question": "If a solution is 105 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 55 ml",
    "Answer": 5775,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 258,
    "Question": "If a solution is 105 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 2 l",
    "Answer": 210,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 259,
    "Question": "If a solution is 6 mg/60 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 360 ml",
    "Answer": 36,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 260,
    "Question": "If a solution is 5 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 75 ml",
    "Answer": 3.75,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 261,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 4.5 g/10 g, how many g are required to make a total of 45 g",
    "Answer": 20.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 262,
    "Question": "If a solution is 4 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 70 ml",
    "Answer": 2.8,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 263,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 0.5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 15 g",
    "Answer": 0.075,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 264,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 2 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 65 g",
    "Answer": 1300,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 265,
    "Question": "If a solution is 80 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 55 ml",
    "Answer": 4400,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 266,
    "Question": "If a solution is 25 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 1 l",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 267,
    "Question": "If a solution is 3.5 mg/70 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 245 ml",
    "Answer": 12.25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 268,
    "Question": "If a solution is 3.5 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 80 ml",
    "Answer": 2.8,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 269,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 4.5 g/70 g, how many g are required to make a total of 315 g",
    "Answer": 20.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 270,
    "Question": "If a solution is 1.5 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 60 ml",
    "Answer": 0.9,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 271,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 5.5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 105 g",
    "Answer": 5.775,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 272,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 2 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 40 g",
    "Answer": 800,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 273,
    "Question": "If a solution is 20 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 80 ml",
    "Answer": 1600,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 274,
    "Question": "If a solution is 90 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 2 l",
    "Answer": 180,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 275,
    "Question": "If a solution is 3.5 mg/50 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 175 ml",
    "Answer": 12.25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 276,
    "Question": "If a solution is 1 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 20 ml",
    "Answer": 0.2,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 277,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 6 g/80 g, how many g are required to make a total of 480 g",
    "Answer": 36,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 278,
    "Question": "If a solution is 2 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 25 ml",
    "Answer": 0.5,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 279,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 0.5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 95 g",
    "Answer": 0.475,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 280,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1.5 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 60 g",
    "Answer": 900,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 281,
    "Question": "If a solution is 45 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 65 ml",
    "Answer": 2925,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 282,
    "Question": "If a solution is 75 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 2 l",
    "Answer": 150,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 283,
    "Question": "If a solution is 3.5 mg/20 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 70 ml",
    "Answer": 12.25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 284,
    "Question": "If a solution is 4 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 20 ml",
    "Answer": 0.8,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 285,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 5 g/100 g, how many g are required to make a total of 500 g",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 286,
    "Question": "If a solution is 9.5 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 55 ml",
    "Answer": 5.225,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 287,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 4.5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 15 g",
    "Answer": 0.675,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 288,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 2 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 30 g",
    "Answer": 600,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 289,
    "Question": "If a solution is 115 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 60 ml",
    "Answer": 6900,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 290,
    "Question": "If a solution is 25 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 0.5 l",
    "Answer": 12.5,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 291,
    "Question": "If a solution is 1.5 mg/80 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 120 ml",
    "Answer": 2.25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 292,
    "Question": "If a solution is 8.5 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 70 ml",
    "Answer": 5.95,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 293,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 2 g/80 g, how many g are required to make a total of 160 g",
    "Answer": 4,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 294,
    "Question": "If a solution is 2 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 110 ml",
    "Answer": 2.2,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 295,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 3 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 80 g",
    "Answer": 2.4,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 296,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 0.5 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 15 g",
    "Answer": 75,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 297,
    "Question": "If a solution is 25 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 120 ml",
    "Answer": 3000,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 298,
    "Question": "If a solution is 30 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 0.5 l",
    "Answer": 15,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 299,
    "Question": "If a solution is 5 mg/40 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 200 ml",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 300,
    "Question": "If a solution is 6 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 100 ml",
    "Answer": 6,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 301,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 4 g/100 g, how many g are required to make a total of 400 g",
    "Answer": 16,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 302,
    "Question": "If a solution is 4.5 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 50 ml",
    "Answer": 2.25,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 303,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 4 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 125 g",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 304,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1.5 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 20 g",
    "Answer": 300,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 305,
    "Question": "If a solution is 65 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 30 ml",
    "Answer": 1950,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 306,
    "Question": "If a solution is 110 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 0.5 l",
    "Answer": 55,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 307,
    "Question": "If a solution is 5.5 mg/30 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 165 ml",
    "Answer": 30.25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 308,
    "Question": "If a solution is 5.5 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 40 ml",
    "Answer": 2.2,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 309,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 6 g/70 g, how many g are required to make a total of 420 g",
    "Answer": 36,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 310,
    "Question": "If a solution is 1 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 45 ml",
    "Answer": 0.45,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 311,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 9 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 100 g",
    "Answer": 9,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 312,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 60 g",
    "Answer": 600,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 313,
    "Question": "If a solution is 105 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 75 ml",
    "Answer": 7875,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 314,
    "Question": "If a solution is 45 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 1 l",
    "Answer": 45,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 315,
    "Question": "If a solution is 1.5 mg/80 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 120 ml",
    "Answer": 2.25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 316,
    "Question": "If a solution is 0.5 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 100 ml",
    "Answer": 0.5,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 317,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 4 g/10 g, how many g are required to make a total of 40 g",
    "Answer": 16,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 318,
    "Question": "If a solution is 9 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 5 ml",
    "Answer": 0.45,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 319,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 6.5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 80 g",
    "Answer": 5.2,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 320,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1.5 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 30 g",
    "Answer": 450,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 321,
    "Question": "If a solution is 45 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 25 ml",
    "Answer": 1125,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 322,
    "Question": "If a solution is 110 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 1 l",
    "Answer": 110,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 323,
    "Question": "If a solution is 3 mg/50 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 150 ml",
    "Answer": 9,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 324,
    "Question": "If a solution is 7 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 15 ml",
    "Answer": 1.05,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 325,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 5 g/50 g, how many g are required to make a total of 250 g",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 326,
    "Question": "If a solution is 6.5 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 50 ml",
    "Answer": 3.25,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 327,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 0.5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 40 g",
    "Answer": 0.2,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 328,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 75 g",
    "Answer": 750,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 329,
    "Question": "If a solution is 120 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 20 ml",
    "Answer": 2400,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 330,
    "Question": "If a solution is 115 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 2 l",
    "Answer": 230,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 331,
    "Question": "If a solution is 5 mg/100 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 500 ml",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 332,
    "Question": "If a solution is 4.5 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 90 ml",
    "Answer": 4.05,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 333,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 6 g/10 g, how many g are required to make a total of 60 g",
    "Answer": 36,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 334,
    "Question": "If a solution is 1.5 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 70 ml",
    "Answer": 1.05,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 335,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1.5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 60 g",
    "Answer": 0.9,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 336,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 0.5 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 15 g",
    "Answer": 75,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 337,
    "Question": "If a solution is 60 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 20 ml",
    "Answer": 1200,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 338,
    "Question": "If a solution is 75 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 1.5 l",
    "Answer": 112.5,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 339,
    "Question": "If a solution is 4.5 mg/50 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 225 ml",
    "Answer": 20.25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 340,
    "Question": "If a solution is 7 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 40 ml",
    "Answer": 2.8,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 341,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 3.5 g/70 g, how many g are required to make a total of 245 g",
    "Answer": 12.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 342,
    "Question": "If a solution is 9.5 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 50 ml",
    "Answer": 4.75,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 343,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 2 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 120 g",
    "Answer": 2.4,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 344,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 2 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 30 g",
    "Answer": 600,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 345,
    "Question": "If a solution is 5 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 95 ml",
    "Answer": 475,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 346,
    "Question": "If a solution is 125 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 1.5 l",
    "Answer": 187.5,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 347,
    "Question": "If a solution is 2.5 mg/70 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 175 ml",
    "Answer": 6.25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 348,
    "Question": "If a solution is 2 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 45 ml",
    "Answer": 0.9,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 349,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 3 g/90 g, how many g are required to make a total of 270 g",
    "Answer": 9,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 350,
    "Question": "If a solution is 0.5 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 5 ml",
    "Answer": 0.025,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 351,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 3.5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 125 g",
    "Answer": 4.375,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 352,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 10 g",
    "Answer": 100,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 353,
    "Question": "If a solution is 95 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 15 ml",
    "Answer": 1425,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 354,
    "Question": "If a solution is 50 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 0.5 l",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 355,
    "Question": "If a solution is 2.5 mg/100 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 250 ml",
    "Answer": 6.25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 356,
    "Question": "If a solution is 10 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 40 ml",
    "Answer": 4,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 357,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 4 g/10 g, how many g are required to make a total of 40 g",
    "Answer": 16,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 358,
    "Question": "If a solution is 9 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 70 ml",
    "Answer": 6.3,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 359,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 8 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 30 g",
    "Answer": 2.4,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 360,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1.5 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 30 g",
    "Answer": 450,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 361,
    "Question": "If a solution is 125 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 90 ml",
    "Answer": 11250,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 362,
    "Question": "If a solution is 35 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 1.5 l",
    "Answer": 52.5,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 363,
    "Question": "If a solution is 6 mg/80 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 480 ml",
    "Answer": 36,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 364,
    "Question": "If a solution is 1.5 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 100 ml",
    "Answer": 1.5,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 365,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 5 g/40 g, how many g are required to make a total of 200 g",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 366,
    "Question": "If a solution is 6 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 60 ml",
    "Answer": 3.6,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 367,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1.5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 110 g",
    "Answer": 1.65,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 368,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 0.5 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 10 g",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 369,
    "Question": "If a solution is 65 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 110 ml",
    "Answer": 7150,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 370,
    "Question": "If a solution is 120 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 2 l",
    "Answer": 240,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 371,
    "Question": "If a solution is 4.5 mg/20 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 90 ml",
    "Answer": 20.25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 372,
    "Question": "If a solution is 6 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 10 ml",
    "Answer": 0.6,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 373,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 3.5 g/20 g, how many g are required to make a total of 70 g",
    "Answer": 12.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 374,
    "Question": "If a solution is 6 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 35 ml",
    "Answer": 2.1,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 375,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 2.5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 25 g",
    "Answer": 0.625,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 376,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1.5 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 75 g",
    "Answer": 1125,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 377,
    "Question": "If a solution is 90 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 10 ml",
    "Answer": 900,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 378,
    "Question": "If a solution is 70 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 1 l",
    "Answer": 70,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 379,
    "Question": "If a solution is 2 mg/30 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 60 ml",
    "Answer": 4,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 380,
    "Question": "If a solution is 3 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 60 ml",
    "Answer": 1.8,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 381,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 4.5 g/40 g, how many g are required to make a total of 180 g",
    "Answer": 20.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 382,
    "Question": "If a solution is 1 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 115 ml",
    "Answer": 1.15,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 383,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 8 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 85 g",
    "Answer": 6.8,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 384,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 35 g",
    "Answer": 350,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 385,
    "Question": "If a solution is 100 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 115 ml",
    "Answer": 11500,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 386,
    "Question": "If a solution is 45 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 1 l",
    "Answer": 45,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 387,
    "Question": "If a solution is 1.5 mg/90 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 135 ml",
    "Answer": 2.25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 388,
    "Question": "If a solution is 0.5 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 10 ml",
    "Answer": 0.05,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 389,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 3.5 g/70 g, how many g are required to make a total of 245 g",
    "Answer": 12.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 390,
    "Question": "If a solution is 0.5 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 110 ml",
    "Answer": 0.55,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 391,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 2.5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 105 g",
    "Answer": 2.625,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 392,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 15 g",
    "Answer": 150,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 393,
    "Question": "If a solution is 45 mg/ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 35 ml",
    "Answer": 1575,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 394,
    "Question": "If a solution is 75 mg/ml, how many g are required to make a total of 0.5 l",
    "Answer": 37.5,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 395,
    "Question": "If a solution is 3.5 mg/50 ml, how many mg are required to make a total of 175 ml",
    "Answer": 12.25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 396,
    "Question": "If a solution is 6.5 %w/v, how many g are required to make a total of 125 ml",
    "Answer": 8.125,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 397,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 4.5 g/60 g, how many g are required to make a total of 270 g",
    "Answer": 20.25,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 398,
    "Question": "If a solution is 6.5 %v/v, how many ml are required to make a total of 90 ml",
    "Answer": 5.85,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 399,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 0.5 %w/w, how many g are required to make a total of 25 g",
    "Answer": 0.125,
    "Units": "g"
  },
  {
    "Number": 400,
    "Question": "If a mixture is 1 %w/w, how many mg are required to make a total of 65 g",
    "Answer": 650,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 401,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 30 mg\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 402,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 227.5 mg\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 65,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 403,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1050 mg\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 35,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 404,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 75 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 405,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 12.5 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 406,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 75 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 407,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 210 mg\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 30,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 408,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 180 mg\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 60,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 409,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 750 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 30,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 410,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 135 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 45,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 411,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 67.5 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 45,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 412,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 975 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 65,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 413,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 260 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 65,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 414,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 212.5 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 85,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 415,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1350 mg\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 45,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 416,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 325 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 65,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 417,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 12.5 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 418,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 200 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 10,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 419,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 680 mg\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 85,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 420,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 297.5 mg\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 85,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 421,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2850 mg\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 95,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 422,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 105 mg\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 15,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 423,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 75 mg\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 424,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 425,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 360 mg\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 45,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 426,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 380 mg\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 95,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 427,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2275 mg\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 65,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 428,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 200 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 429,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 100 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 430,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2125 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 85,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 431,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 150 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 432,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 260 mg\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 65,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 433,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1300 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 65,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 434,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 600 mg\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 75,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 435,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 142.5 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 95,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 436,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 600 mg\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 15,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 437,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 455 mg\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 65,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 438,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 80 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 40,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 439,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 875 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 35,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 440,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 75 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 15,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 441,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 112.5 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 45,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 442,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1425 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 95,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 443,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 600 mg\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 75,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 444,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 225 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 445,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 175 mg\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 446,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 440 mg\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 55,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 447,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 30 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 15,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 448,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 3600 mg\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 449,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 35 mg\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 450,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 180 mg\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 45,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 451,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 375 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 452,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 105 mg\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 15,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 453,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 100 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 454,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 500 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 455,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 600 mg\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 75,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 456,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 192.5 mg\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 55,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 457,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2450 mg\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 70,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 458,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 270 mg\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 45,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 459,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 105 mg\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 35,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 460,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 100 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 461,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 760 mg\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 95,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 462,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 127.5 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 85,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 463,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2625 mg\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 75,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 464,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 25 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 465,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 285 mg\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 95,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 466,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 450 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 30,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 467,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 35 mg\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 468,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 40 mg\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 10,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 469,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 200 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 10,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 470,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 225 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 75,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 471,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 225 mg\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 75,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 472,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 600 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 40,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 473,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 300 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 60,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 474,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 250 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 100,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 475,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1350 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 476,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 560 mg\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 477,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 25 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 10,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 478,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1800 mg\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 60,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 479,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 180 mg\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 30,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 480,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 60 mg\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 15,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 481,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1400 mg\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 40,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 482,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 30 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 10,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 483,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 20 mg\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 484,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2200 mg\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 55,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 485,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 160 mg\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 20,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 486,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 60 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 40,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 487,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 488,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 60 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 20,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 489,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 105 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 70,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 490,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1800 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 491,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 325 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 65,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 492,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 25 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 10,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 493,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1500 mg\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 494,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 60 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 20,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 495,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 380 mg\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 95,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 496,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 3325 mg\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 95,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 497,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 245 mg\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 35,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 498,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 227.5 mg\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 65,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 499,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 600 mg\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 20,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 500,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 140 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 35,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 501,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 100 mg\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 502,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 14.7 g\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 420,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 503,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2.56 g\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 320,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 504,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1.2 g\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 400,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 505,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 4.8 g\n\nDrug available as: 15mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 320,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 506,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1.04 g\n\nDrug available as: 20mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 260,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 507,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1.925 g\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 550,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 508,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 3.75 g\n\nDrug available as: 15mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 250,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 509,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 3.08 g\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 440,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 510,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1 g\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 400,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 511,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 8 g\n\nDrug available as: 20mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 400,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 512,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1.53 g\n\nDrug available as: 15mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 510,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 513,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1.56 g\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 390,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 514,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 22 g\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 550,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 515,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2.7 g\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 450,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 516,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1.68 g\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 560,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 517,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 6.25 g\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 250,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 518,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 4.08 g\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 510,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 519,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1.96 g\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 560,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 520,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 10.5 g\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 300,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 521,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2.16 g\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 270,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 522,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1.08 g\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 360,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 523,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 6.8 g\n\nDrug available as: 20mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 340,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 524,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2.04 g\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 340,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 525,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1.24 g\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 310,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 526,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 8 g\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 320,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 527,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 3.57 g\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 510,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 528,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 0.975 g\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 390,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 529,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 7.35 g\n\nDrug available as: 15mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 490,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 530,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2.16 g\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 360,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 531,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1.04 g\n\nDrug available as: 20mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 520,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 532,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 12 g\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 480,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 533,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 3.6 g\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 600,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 534,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1.18 g\n\nDrug available as: 20mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 590,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 535,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 12 g\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 480,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 536,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 3.71 g\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 530,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 537,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 0.945 g\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 270,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 538,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 24 g\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 600,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 539,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2 g\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 250,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 540,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 0.525 g\n\nDrug available as: 15mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 350,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 541,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 19.6 g\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 490,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 542,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1.5 g\n\nDrug available as: 15mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 500,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 543,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1.14 g\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 380,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 544,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 20.8 g\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 520,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 545,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1.8 g\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 360,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 546,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 0.5 g\n\nDrug available as: 20mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 250,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 547,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 5 g\n\nDrug available as: 20mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 250,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 548,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2.94 g\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 490,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 549,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1.59 g\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 530,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 550,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 16.45 g\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 470,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 551,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1.36 g\n\nDrug available as: 20mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 340,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 552,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 0.91 g\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 260,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 553,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 10.8 g\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 270,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 554,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2.24 g\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 320,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 555,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1.04 g\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 260,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 556,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 13.6 g\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 340,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 557,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 3.22 g\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 460,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 558,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 0.56 g\n\nDrug available as: 20mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 280,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 559,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 8.1 g\n\nDrug available as: 15mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 540,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 560,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1.8 g\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 360,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 561,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2.08 g\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 520,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 562,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 11.75 g\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 470,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 563,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2.58 g\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 430,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 564,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 0.54 g\n\nDrug available as: 20mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 270,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 565,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 12.6 g\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 420,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 566,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2.28 g\n\nDrug available as: 20mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 570,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 567,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 0.75 g\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 250,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 568,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 19.25 g\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 550,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 569,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1.89 g\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 270,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 570,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2.03 g\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 580,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 571,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 9 g\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 300,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 572,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2.52 g\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 360,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 573,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 0.435 g\n\nDrug available as: 15mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 290,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 574,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 12.9 g\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 430,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 575,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 4.32 g\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 540,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 576,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1.12 g\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 320,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 577,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 13.6 g\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 340,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 578,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1.2 g\n\nDrug available as: 20mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 300,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 579,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1.8 g\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 450,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 580,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 9.9 g\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 330,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 581,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 4.24 g\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 530,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 582,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 0.85 g\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 340,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 583,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 12.25 g\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 490,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 584,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2.7 g\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 540,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 585,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1.35 g\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 450,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 586,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 13.25 g\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 530,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 587,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2.75 g\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 550,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 588,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1.41 g\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 470,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 589,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 7.5 g\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 250,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 590,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2.24 g\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 280,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 591,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 0.96 g\n\nDrug available as: 30mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 320,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 592,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 21 g\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 600,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 593,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 0.78 g\n\nDrug available as: 15mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 260,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 594,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1.715 g\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 490,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 595,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 5.6 g\n\nDrug available as: 20mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 280,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 596,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2.94 g\n\nDrug available as: 35mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 420,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 597,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 0.6 g\n\nDrug available as: 20mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 300,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 598,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 14.8 g\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 370,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 599,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1.88 g\n\nDrug available as: 20mg/5ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 470,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 600,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1.225 g\n\nDrug available as: 25mg/10ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 490,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 601,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 20.8 g\n\nDrug available as: 40mg/ml\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 520,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 602,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 13.5 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 603,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 4000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 10 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 40,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 604,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 12750 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 85,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 605,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 21250 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 85,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 606,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 10,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 607,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 5000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 20,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 608,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 16000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 609,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 5000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 610,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 28500 mg\n\nDrug available as: 30 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 95,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 611,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 4750 mg\n\nDrug available as: 5 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 95,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 612,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 16250 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 65,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 613,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 8000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 10 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 614,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 15000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 60,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 615,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 3750 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 616,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 16500 mg\n\nDrug available as: 30 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 55,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 617,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 6500 mg\n\nDrug available as: 10 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 65,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 618,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 4000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 20,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 619,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 27000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 30 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 620,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 10000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 621,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 9000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 60,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 622,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 750 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 623,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 12500 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 624,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 11250 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 75,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 625,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1250 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 626,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 21250 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 85,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 627,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 8000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 40,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 628,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 500 mg\n\nDrug available as: 10 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 629,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 3500 mg\n\nDrug available as: 10 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 35,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 630,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 5000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 5 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 100,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 631,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 30000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 30 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 100,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 632,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 20000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 633,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 3000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 10 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 30,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 634,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 9000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 45,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 635,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 4000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 10 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 40,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 636,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 10500 mg\n\nDrug available as: 30 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 35,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 637,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1500 mg\n\nDrug available as: 5 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 30,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 638,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 9750 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 65,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 639,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 10000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 40,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 640,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2500 mg\n\nDrug available as: 5 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 641,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 9750 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 65,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 642,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 27000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 30 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 643,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 16250 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 65,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 644,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 6000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 10 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 60,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 645,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 13500 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 646,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 3000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 15,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 647,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 750 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 648,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 5000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 5 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 100,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 649,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 3000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 15,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 650,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 16250 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 65,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 651,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 11250 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 45,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 652,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 6000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 30,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 653,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 9000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 30 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 30,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 654,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1500 mg\n\nDrug available as: 10 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 15,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 655,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 1250 mg\n\nDrug available as: 5 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 656,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 3750 mg\n\nDrug available as: 5 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 75,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 657,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 5 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 40,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 658,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 7000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 10 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 70,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 659,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 14250 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 95,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 660,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 5 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 40,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 661,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 12750 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 85,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 662,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 9500 mg\n\nDrug available as: 10 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 95,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 663,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 11000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 55,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 664,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 5000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 665,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 16250 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 65,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 666,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 3500 mg\n\nDrug available as: 10 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 35,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 667,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 9500 mg\n\nDrug available as: 10 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 95,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 668,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 250 mg\n\nDrug available as: 5 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 669,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2750 mg\n\nDrug available as: 5 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 55,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 670,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 4000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 5 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 671,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 22500 mg\n\nDrug available as: 30 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 75,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 672,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 10500 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 70,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 673,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 4000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 10 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 40,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 674,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 18000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 675,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 7500 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 676,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 8500 mg\n\nDrug available as: 10 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 85,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 677,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 16000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 678,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 16250 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 65,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 679,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 5250 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 35,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 680,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 12500 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 681,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2250 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 15,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 682,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 3000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 30 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 10,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 683,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 25500 mg\n\nDrug available as: 30 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 85,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 684,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 13750 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 55,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 685,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 750 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 686,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 10000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 687,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2500 mg\n\nDrug available as: 10 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 688,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 3000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 10 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 30,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 689,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 19500 mg\n\nDrug available as: 30 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 65,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 690,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 5250 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 35,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 691,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 2250 mg\n\nDrug available as: 5 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 45,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 692,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 4000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 5 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 693,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 7000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 35,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 694,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 9500 mg\n\nDrug available as: 10 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 95,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 695,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 4500 mg\n\nDrug available as: 5 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 696,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 9000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 10 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 697,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 18000 mg\n\nDrug available as: 20 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 698,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 21250 mg\n\nDrug available as: 25 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 85,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 699,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 5250 mg\n\nDrug available as: 15 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 35,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 700,
    "Question": "Prescription for: 500 mg\n\nDrug available as: 10 %w/v\n\nHow many ml are required for the dose?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "ml"
  }
]
